A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Jobs, 1
  - 277 - Archives of American Art, Detroit Institute of Art, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 265)
  - 278 - Central Michigan University Teacher Education, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 266)
  - 279 - Johns Hopkins University: African Studies Foreign Area Training Fellowships, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 267)
  - 280 - Pangborn Blvd. Elementary School and Educational Television Center, Hagerstown, Md., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 268)
  - 281 - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 269)
  - 282 - American Political Science Association Congressional Internship Program, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - 283 - Oregon State System of Higher Education - Inter-Institutional Television Teaching Project, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 271)
    Photographer: Vermilya, Carl
  - 284 - In-School television, Atlanta, Georgia, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 272)
    Photographer: Leipzig, Arthur
  - 285 - In-school television, Marbury High School - Alabama, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - 286 - WGBH Boston, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 274)
  - 287 - Learning Lens 1, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 275)
  - 288 - Learning Lens 1, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 276)
    Photographer: Simmons, William. Images taken from film strips for ETV pictorial.
  - 289 - Great Cities School Improvement Program: Milwaukee (ED, PA, YD), 1960 December (Box 19, Folder 277)
  - 290 - Great Cities: School Improvement Program, St. Louis, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 278)
  - 291 - Chicago Boys Clubs, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 279)
  - 292 - Pilot Project in Local Services for Older People, Marion County, Kansas, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 280)
  - 293 - Rand Corporation Urban Transportation Study, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 281)
  - 294 - Tamarind Lithography Workshop, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - 295 - San Francisco Actors Workshop, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - 296 - Hofstra College (File Missing), 1960 December (Box 20, Folder 284)
    Photographer: Simmons, William. No prints or negatives available. File is missing.
  - 297 - Community Development: Banskho Village, Rajasthan, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - 298A - Training of Village Workers: Gandhigram, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - 298B - Training of Village Workers: Manipur, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - 299 - Training of Village Workers: Small Industries Program, Ludhiana, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 288)
  - 300 - Nilokheri Community Development, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 289)
  - 301 - Extensions Center, Ambala, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 290)
  - 302 - Rajasthan, Hyderabad, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 291)
    Photographer: Hertz, Willard
  - 303 - Training of Village Workers, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 292)
  - 304 - Urban Community Development, Delhi, Instep India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 293)
  - 305 - Instep Graduates at Work, Rourkala Steel Plant, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 294)
  - 306 - Instep Graduates at Work, Rourkala Steel Plant, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 295)
  - 307 - Small Industries Program, Ludhiana, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 296)
  - 308 - Poonamalee, India, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 297)
  - 309 - Research in the Negev, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 298)
    Israel
  - 310 - Central Institute of English, Hyderabad Footwear Training Centre, Madras, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 299)
  - 311 - Midwest Program on Airborne Television Instruction, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - 312 - New York University Cooperative Program with Government Agencies, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 301)
  - 313 - Hofstra College Undergraduate Education, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 302)
  - 314 - Association Colleges of the Midwest Higher Education, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 303)
  - 315 - Princeton University: Graduate Training in Plasma Physics, New Jersey, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 304)
  - 316 - Community Demonstration Project on Aging, Worcester, Mass. Brandeis Univ., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 305)
  - 317 - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Reproductive Health and Population, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 306)
  - 318 - Great Cities School Improvement Project: Philadelphia, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 307)
  - 319 - Ballet Society (School of American Ballet: School of San Francisco Ballet), New York, California, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 308)
    Photographer: Lichtner, Marvin
  - 320 - Rutgers University: Woman and Mathematics Teacher Training, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 309)
  - 321 - Williams College: Economics Study and Teaching, Massachusetts, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 310)
  - 322 - University of Wisconsin: Urban Extension Program, Madison, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 311)
  - 323 - University of Wisconsin Economics Research, Computer Research, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 312)
  - 324 - Case Institute of Technology Systems Research Center and Engineering Design Center, Ohio, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 313)
  - 325 - Great Cities School Improvements Project, Detroit, Michigan, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 314)
  - 326 - National Council of Scientific and Technical Investigators, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 315)
  - 327 - University of Michigan Demography Center, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 316)
  - 328 - New Jersey State Board of Control: Rehabilitation of Delinquent Boys, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 317)
  - 329 - Wilkes College, Wilkes Barre (Urban and Regional Studies), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 318)
  - 330 - Brazilian Institute for Education Science and Culture, Sao Paolo, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    Brazil
  - 331 - Getulio Vargas Foundation, Rio de Janeiro: applied economic research, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 320)
  - 332 - Board of Higher Education: New York City Public Service Internship Program, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 321)
  - 333 - University of Missouri and Training of College Teachers, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 322)
  - 334 - Kansas City Association of Trust and Foundations, Missouri, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 323)
  - 335 - University of Buenos Aires: Sociology Study and Teaching, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 324)
    Photographer: Frank, Renata
    Argentina
  - 336 - Institute Politique Congolaise, Leopoldville: strengthening public administration, The Congo, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 325)
    Photographer: Surbez, Jacques
    Zaire
  - 337 - Institute for Public Administration: Urban Transportation, New York, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 326)
    Photographer: Lichner, Marvin
  - 338 - Youth Studies Center, Santa Monica, CA (YD), 1961 October (Box 22, Folder 327)
  - 339 - County of Los Angeles Group Guidance Service (YD), 1961 October (Box 22, Folder 328)
  - 340 - American Friends Service Committee (Youth for Service) (YD), 1961 October (Box 22, Folder 329)
  - 341 - Richmond, California Neighborhood House (YD), 1961 October (Box 22, Folder 330)
  - 342 - Richard Magat's European Trip: North Atlantic Partnership, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 331)
    Photographer: Magat, Richard
    Europe
  - 343 - New York State: Legislative Internship Program, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 332)
  - 344 - New York City Board of Education: Municipal Cooperative Education and Work Program, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 333)
  - 345 - Russian Exchange Students, Cornell University: American-Soviet Inter-University Exchange Program, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 334)
  - 346 - Georgetown University Institute of Languages and Linguistics: English as a Second Language, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 335)
  - 347 - Fellowship Loan Program, Illinois Institute of Technology: Engineering: Study and Teaching Fellowship Loan Program, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 336)
  - 348 - Purdue University, Calumet Center: Urban Renewal, Indiana, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 337)
  - 349 - Family Services Association of Tampa: Problems of the Aging, The Economic Growth Center, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 338)
  - 350 - Yale University, New Haven: Economics - Research, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 339)
  - 351 - Peabody Conservatory of Music, Baltimore: Young American Conductors, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 340)
  - 352 - Southern Police Institute, Univ. of Louisville, Kentucky, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 341)
  - 353 - Jefferson County Fiscal Court: Southfield Rehabilitation Center; Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Development, Kentucky, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 342)
  - 354 - University of Pittsburgh Computation and Data Processing Center: Information Retrieval; legal research, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 343)
  - 355 - University of Pittsburgh, Fellowships Loan Program: Engineering-Study and Searching, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 344)
  - 356 - ACTION HOUSING Pittsburgh: Urban and Regional Studies, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 345)
  - 357 - Cornell University area studies: Agricultural and Rural development, New York, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 346, Box 139, Folder 1983)
  - 358 - Princeton University Humanities Study, New Jersey, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 347)
  - 359 - Rutgers University Urban Studies Center: Rutgers Urban Fellowship, New Jersey, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 348)
  - 360 - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn: Engineering education, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 349)
  - 361 - Oregon State Department of Education: Comprehensive School Improvement Program (CSIP): Teacher Education, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 350)
  - 362 - University of Oregon: Institute of International Studies, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 351)
  - 363 - Family Service Association, Oakland, CA., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 352)
  - 364 - Great Cities, Gray Areas, Oakland: Community Development, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 353)
  - 365 - Teacher Training, Swarthmore College, Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 354)
  - 366 - Special Program in Education, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 355)
  - 367 - Vocational Educational, Rural Development, Agricultural Development Middle East, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 356)
    Photographer: Keenan, Terry
    United Arab Republic (UAR)
  - 368 - New York Medical College: Pre-school Education, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 357)
  - 369 - Brentwood L.I. School System: Comprehensive School Improvement Program (CSIP), New York, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 358)
  - 370 - Council on Library Resources, Yale U. Press: Conservation and Preservation: Scholarship in the Humanities, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 359)
  - 371 - Brooklyn College-Scope Theatre of the Street: Juvenile delinquency and youth development, New York, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 360)
  - 372 - University of Oklahoma Experimental Program in Urban Sciences, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 361)
  - 373 - Mummers Theatre, Oklahoma City, 1963 April (Box 23, Folder 362)
    Oklahoma
  - 374 - Dade County Board of Public Instruction: Elementary Education; Secondary Education, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 363)
  - 375 - University of Florida Teacher Education, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 364)
  - 376 - University of Rochester: Teacher Education, New York., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 365)
  - 377 - McGill University: Institute of Air and Space Law: International Legal Studies, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 366)
  - 378 - McGill University Institute of Islamic Studies, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 367)
  - 379 - Baltimore Board of Education Preschool Education: Maryland, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - 380 - Asian Studies, Sweet Briar, Lynchburg, Randolph-Macon: Area Studies - Virginia, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 369)
  - 381 - Vanderbilt University: Research and Training in Reproductive Physiology: Tennessee, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 370)
  - 382 - Great Cities, Gray Areas, New Haven: Community Development: Connecticut, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 371)
  - 383 - Institutes of Judicial Administration: Vera Foundation: New York, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 372)
  - 384 - National Legal Aid and Defender Association, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 373)
  - 385 - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA): Research in Reproductive Physiology: Contraceptive Research: California, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 374)
    Photographer: Munroe, Joe
  - 386 - Special Centre for English Language, Nairobi, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 375)
    Photographer: Thal, Maria
    Kenya
  - 387 - Nairobi Science Teaching Center, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 376)
  - 388 - Coryndon Museum, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 377)
  - 389 - Civil Service Training Centre: Dar Es Salaam, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 378)
    Photographer: Amin, Mohamid
    Tanganyika
  - 390 - Tanganyika Gap Program, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 379)
  - 391 - Georgetown University Population Studies, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 380)
  - 392 - Marine Biological Laboratory: Training of Specialists in Classification of Marine Organisms, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 381)
  - 393 - National Academy of Science, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 382)
  - 394 - International Affairs, OECD (Mediterranean Regional Project), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 383)
  - 395 - Humanities and Arts program (H&A), 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 384)
  - 396 - Aging Golden Years Cover, 1963 October (Box 24, Folder 385)
  - 397 - Institute of Land Reclamation, 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 386)
    Egypt
  - 398 - Overseas Development, Middle East U.A.R. National Industrial Management Board, 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 387)
  - 399 - Overseas Development, Middle East (Turkey) Middle East Technical University, 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 388)
    Turkey
  - 400 - Overseas Development, Middle East (Turkey) Economic and Social Studies Conference Board, 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 389)
  - 401 - Overseas Development, Middle East (Lebanon) Civil Service Training Board, Beirut College for Women, Magassed School, Institute of Vocational and Technical Education., 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 390)
  - 402 - Industry Institute, 1963 August (Box 24, Folder 391)
  - 403 - Education Comprehensive School Improvement Program: Richmond, Virginia, 1964 March (Box 24, Folder 392)
  - 404 - Action for Boston Community Development, 1964 March (Box 24, Folder 393)
  - 405 - Indiana Language Program, 1964 March (Box 24, Folder 394)
  - 407 - Greater Cleveland Associated Foundation, 1964 March (Box 24, Folder 396)
  - 406 - University of Illinois - Labor Relations, 1964 March (Box 24, Folder 395)
    Photographer: Simmons, William. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 408 - Duke University: International Studies, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 397)
  - 409 - University of Tenn-Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 398)
  - 410 - International Training and Research (ITR) Fellowship Program for Peace Corps Veterans, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 399)
    Photographer: Lichtner, M.
  - 411 - Phoenix Welfare Foundation Project in Pupil Motivation, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 400)
    Photographer: Monroe, Joe
  - 412 - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) American Studies, University of Oslo (International Affairs program), 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 401)
    Norway
  - 413 - Institute of Social Studies, The Hague (International Affairs program), 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 402)
  - 414 - Ford Foundation in Berlin, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 403)
  - 415 - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1964 April (Box 25, Folder 404)
  - 416 - Humanities and Arts program (H&A), 1964 May (Box 25, Folder 405)
  - 417 - Humanities and Arts program (H&A), 1964 May (Box 25, Folder 406)
  - 418 - Composer-In-Residence, Pittsburgh (Philip Glass), 1964 June (Box 25, Folder 407)
  - 419 - Education and Urban Pittsburgh Team Teaching, Miller School Hill District, Golden Triangle, 1964 June (Box 25, Folder 408)
  - 420 - Jefferson Medical College Student Research in Reproductive Biology, 1964 June (Box 25, Folder 409)
  - 421 - P.A. Regional Planning Association, 1964 June (Box 25, Folder 410)
  - 422 - Population Student Research in Reproductive Biology: Cornell Medical College, 1964 June (Box 25, Folder 411)
  - 423 - National Association of Independent Schools: Summer Enrichment Program, 1964 July 10 (Box 25, Folder 412)
  - 424 - Public Affairs program - Howard University Foreign Affairs Scholars Program, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 413)
  - 425 - University of Wisconsin Study of Retraining of Unemployed Workers, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 414)
  - 426 - Palmer Memorial Institute Summer Enrichment Program, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 415)
    Photographer: Homer Page
  - 427 - India Family Planning: All-India Institute of Medical Sciences, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 416)
    Photographer: Three Lions, Chowdhurry/ Grewal
  - 428 - International Training and Research (I.T.R.) Columbia University Study Fellowships in Latin American Studies, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 417)
    Photographer: Berson, Theodore
  - 429 - Columbia, 1964 November (Box 25, Folder 418)
    Columbia
  - 430 - Venezuela (Oriente University et al), 1964 November (Box 25, Folder 419)
    Venezuela
  - 431 - New Building Action, Inc., 1964 May (Box 26, Folder 420, Box 134, Folder 1947)
  - 432 - Pretechnology Program in San Francisco High Schools; Project FEAST, 1965 May (Box 26, Folder 421)
  - 433 - City College of San Francisco Vocational Program: Hotel Restaurant Studies, 1965 May (Box 26, Folder 422)
  - 434 - MAT Program: Vanderbilt, 1965 May (Box 26, Folder 423)
    Photographer: Rutledge, Don
  - 435 - Dept. of Education Curriculum Center, Mayaguez, Puerto Rico, 1965 May (Box 26, Folder 424)
  - 436 - Manhattan Summers Project, 1965 May (Box 26, Folder 425)
  - 437 - Rural Farming: Eastern Region, 1965 April (Box 26, Folder 426)
    Photographer: Wilcox, Elizabeth
  - 438 - University of Nigeria: Economic Development Institute, 1965 April (Box 26, Folder 427)
  - 439 - National Library of Nigeria, 1965 April (Box 26, Folder 428)
  - 440 - Stout State University Vocational Education (Box 26, Folder 429)
    Photographer: McCoy, Dan
  - 441 - Public Affairs program - Leaves for Fellowship American Political Science Assn., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 430)
    Photographer: Karp, Martin
  - 442 - Association of American Law Schools (Box 26, Folder 431)
    Photographer: Roodman, Carl
  - 443 - Public Affairs program - Action Pac., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 432)
  - 444 - H&I Fordham Conference on Pierre De Teilhard Chardin (Box 26, Folder 433)
  - 445 - American Society for Engineering Education (Box 26, Folder 434)
    Photographer: McAllister, Bruce
  - 446 - Indian Coverage Punjab Wheat Market, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 435)
    Photographer: Singh, Raghubir
  - 447 - New York Family Planning Institute: Reproductive Biology (Box 26, Folder 436)
  - 448 - Indian Research and Training: Delhi University Reproductive Biology, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 437)
  - 449 - Agricultural Implements and Power Development Center, Allahabad, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 438)
  - 450 - India Calcutta Intensive Family Planning Program, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 439)
  - 451 - India Delphi Fertility Survey, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 440)
  - 452 - Frank Stimley at Columbia, National Achievement Award Scholarship, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 441)
  - 453 - Robert Bennett: National Achievement Scholarship: Dartmouth, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 442)
    Photographer: Massar, Ivan
  - 454 - Walker Art Center Museum Curatorial Intern, 1965 October (Box 27, Folder 443)
  - 455 - University of Wisconsin International Programs (Box 27, Folder 444)
  - 456 - American Council on Education Academic Administrative Internship Program. Dr. Hornbick, Adm. Vice-Pres., 1966 March (Box 27, Folder 445)
  - 457 - Education School Improvement: Englewood, New Jersey School District, 1966 April (Box 27, Folder 446)
  - 458 - Skills: Scholarship and the Public Service, 1966 April (Box 27, Folder 447)
    Photographer: Bachmann, Herman
  - 459 - Madras, India Rice Farmer, 1966 June (Box 27, Folder 448)
  - 460 - Calcutta Bustee Girl, 1966 June (Box 27, Folder 449, Box 134, Folder 1948)
    Photographer: Unknown (Singh?)
  - 461 - Oceanographic Institute, Sao Paolo., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 450)
    Photographer: Rutledge, Don Black Star
  - 462 - Family Planning in Bahia, Brazil, Federal University of Bahia, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 451)
  - 463 - Rural University of the State of Minas Gerais, 1966 Spring (Box 28, Folder 452)
  - 464 - University of Buenos Aires, 1966 June (Box 28, Folder 453)
  - 465 - University of Salvador, 1966 June (Box 28, Folder 454)
    El Salvador
  - 466 - University of Costa Rica, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 455)
    Costa Rica
  - 467 - American School of Guatemala, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 456)
    Guatemala
  - 468 - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 457)
    Photographer: Ward, Fred
  - 469 - Institute for Criminal Justice/Georgetown U., 1966 July (Box 28, Folder 458)
  - 470 - Michigan State University, 1966 July (Box 28, Folder 459)
    Photographer: Seaver, Robert
  - 471 - Texas Southern University: Business School, 1966 August (Box 28, Folder 460)
    Photographer: St. Gil, Marc
  - 472 - Opportunities Industrialization Center?Los Angeles, 1966 August (Box 29, Folder 461)
    Photographer: Daniels, Gene
  - 473 - Foundation Exhibit: Durham Reports Education Improvement Program, 1967 February (Box 29, Folder 462)
    Photographer: Watterson, Libby
  - 474 - New Jersey Department of Education Technology for Children Project, 1967 May (Box 29, Folder 463)
  - 475 - Ford Foundation Exhibit: "Package Program", 1967 May (Box 29, Folder 464)
    Photographer: Leo Choplin (B. Star)
  - 476 - Pakistan: Peshawar & Near Montgomery - Comilla - Black Star, 1967 July (Box 29, Folder 465)
  - 477 - Institute for International Education, Hungary, 1967 July (Box 29, Folder 466)
    Photographer: Wolff, Werner
    Hungary
  - 478 - Project Opportunity, 1968 March (Box 29, Folder 467)
  - 479 - Somali Prime Minister at Ford Foundation, 1968 March (Box 29, Folder 468)
  - 480 - New York Studio School, New York City, 1968 May (Box 29, Folder 469)
    Photographer: Forbes, Robin
  - 481 - New York City Police Precinct Receptionist Program, 1968 June (Box 29, Folder 470)
    Photographer: Levine, Ellen
  - 482 - Two Bridges, New York City, 1968 June (Box 29, Folder 471)
  - 483 - General Specialty Contractor's Association, 1968 August (Box 29, Folder 472)
  - 484 - Conference of California, 1968 August (Box 29, Folder 473)
    Photographer: Berkeley, Judges
  - 485 - Teachers, Inc.: IS 201, New York City, 1968 August (Box 30, Folder 474)
    Photographer: Clark, Bob
  - 486 - Rio de Janiero and Sao Paolo, 1968 September (Box 30, Folder 475)
    Photographer: Love, Claudia
  - 487 - Film Culture Non-Profit Corp., 1968 September (Box 30, Folder 476)
    Photographer: Shapiro, Steve
  - 488 - Alliance High School, Kenya, 1968 November (Box 30, Folder 477)
    Photographer: Serrallier, Michael
  - 489 - Haile Selassie I INTL University, Ethiopia, 1968 December (Box 30, Folder 478)
    Ethiopia
  - 490 - Humanities and Arts program (HA) - Detroit Symphony Orchestra with John McAuliffe, FF Trainee, 1969 February (Box 30, Folder 479)
    Photographer: Benyas-Kaufman
  - 491 - Humanities and Arts program (HA) - Nelson Gallery with Marc Wilson, Ford Foundation Intern, 1969 February (Box 30, Folder 480, Box 134, Folder 1949)
    Photographer: Harvey, Dave
  - 492 - Mark Taper Forum with W. Wingate, 1969 March (Box 30, Folder 481)
  - 493 - International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, 1969 April (Box 30, Folder 482)
    Photographer: Foote, James
  - 494 - Nigeria-Ibadan, International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1969 April (Box 31, Folder 483)
    Photographer: Tolles, Robert
  - 495 - Manchester Business School, 1969 May (Box 31, Folder 484)
    Photographer: Clifton, Alan
    United Kingdom
  - 496 - University of California, Berkeley - Demography, 1969 May (Box 31, Folder 485)
    Photographer: Brown, Dean
  - 497 - University of Geneva: Genetic Epistemology, 1969 May (Box 31, Folder 486)
    Photographer: Sarver, Carlton
  - 498 - School of Medicine: Harbor Hospital, LA, 1969 June (Box 31, Folder 487)
  - 499 - Choreometrics Project - Humanities and Arts program (HA): Columbia University, 1969 June (Box 31, Folder 488)
  - 500 - Metro Denver Fair Housing Center, 1969 July (Box 31, Folder 489)
  - 501 - Doctoral Fellowships for Black Students, South Carolina, 1969 August (Box 31, Folder 490)
    Photographer: Barnes, Billy
  - 502 - Dayton Urban Corps, 1969 June (Box 31, Folder 491)
    Photographer: Hawn, Declan
  - 503 - New Detroit, Inc., 1969 September (Box 31, Folder 492)
  - 504 - Inner City Business Improvement Forum, 1969 September (Box 31, Folder 493)
  - 505 - Harvard University Solid Waste Study (Box 31, Folder 494)
    Photographer: Zimburg, George